Quarterly results are also going to be announced.
Many people also discussed the results announced yesterday.
And because the
people who are constantly tracking the quarterly results
and the traders, the
retail traders, are
also trying to take more bets in it.  In
such a situation, Sir, first of all here we will talk about
Tech Mahindra whose quarterly
results have been announced.  There was a
decline of about 4.5% in profit here.  There was a
profit of ₹194 crore.  A
slight growth of 5.1% was seen in revenue
here.  Also,
margins were seen increasing here.  The margin
for Tech Mahindra was around 12.14%,
which if we
talk about the same quarter of last year,
was around 9.61% at that time.  Apart from this, the company has
also announced an interim dividend of ₹15 per
share.  Tech Mahindra is included in today's loser list.
Sir, what is the view being formed regarding Tech Mahindra
?   According to which the
numbers have been announced.  Does
n't look that impressive.  Inspite,
only marginal improvement
is visible.  Somewhere or the other, profit is
visible but all time high PAT is not
visible yet.  So somewhere
I feel that the stock is underperforming price wise
also.
We can see the lower top lower bottom formation on daily charts as well as
weekly charts.
So somewhere I feel that
unless there is a trend reversal and like
we just had a level specific discussion about the IT index.  There could be
consolidation between 35,000 and 36,000.  So
according to me, some consolation can still be achieved in Tech Mahindra.  Let's take a look at the
range.  There
is a very important range at the bottom around ₹100
and there is a very important resistance at the top
near ₹1500.  So once we are
above the 1500 levels, we are sustaining.
Then we can assume that a good
reversal is in the making for this stock.
We are currently trading below that level.  So
I think the bottom may retest once.  The
joint level there was 1400.
Sir, is there any reversal visible at the levels of 1400?
We should wait and watch a bit there.
So the stock should be
kept in a bit of wait and watch mode for now.   So,
you will have to wait a little for Tech Mahindra.  Here
you will have to adopt the wait and watch strategy.
Sir, you told me about the levels above 1500.  If it goes up from there then
yes exactly 1500 is a very good area
of ​​resistance.  Breakout Needed.
Ok.  So, 1500 is the level from where
you can have a breakout expectation somewhere.
But for now you will have to
wait here for a while.  Okay sir, the next
counter is also from the IT sector.
Here, Persistent Systems also
announced its quarter two results and a
very good jump of about 45% in profit was
seen here and
its profit was around Rs 471 crore.
Revenue also saw a growth of 23%.
Its revenue was around ₹3580 crore.
Margins also appeared to be increasing.
Last year, the margins were 14%.
This year, margins increased to 16.3% in quarter two.
Apart from this,
if we look at the revenue in dollar terms,
we saw a jump of about 17% there.
Revenue in quarter two of this year was Rs 406 million.
If we talk about last year, in quarter two alone, it was
$345 million.
Sir, what is the view being formed regarding the persistent system?
Good profits are also coming from here and
somewhere it is seen outperforming even the big players.
Sir,
in such a situation, what view is being formed here regarding persistent
?
Ankit ji the numbers are excellent.  Very
good numbers have been posted.  Profit
after tax is at an all-time high and margins have been
improving and good
sales data is also showing improvement.
So overall, we can say that fundamentally
very good strong numbers have been posted
and the index is also giving a very good outperformance.
Comparatively speaking, if we
look at the Nifty IT index and talk about the peer stocks,
after Coach, there is Persion Systems
which is coming at number two and has been a good
outperformer among the IT sector
stocks.  So I feel that as far as the
technical structure is concerned,
we are approaching important levels.
5650 5650 is the resistance of a good swing high
which we crossed today.
I feel if today
's closing is achieved at the level of 5650 then definitely it
is a bullish sign for the Persion System and
in the coming time, in the short term, I feel it can
show levels up to 6200.
So, a buying advice is being made in this for short to medium term.
We can buy at these levels only.  In fact, if there is
any downtrend
around 5550, then also we cannot add position.  The
stop loss that we have to maintain is
5350. We have to maintain a stop loss of 5350.   So, in the case of
Persistence System, whose
results were announced today, a profit jump of about 45% is being
seen
and a similar
impact was seen on their share price today.  A
rise of around 6% is being seen right now.  The
level of 5650 is
playing a huge resistance here.
As told by Yagnesh Sir.  If
we have just crossed from there.  But
from here, if you want to take a medium term view, then you have
said around 6200 sir.   Yes
exactly yes.
Your targets up to 6200 can be
seen here.  But the stop
loss that you have to place here should be around
5350.  And remember this is for the medium
term.  And if you have a short term
view then you will have to take a little cautious approach here.
But if you
want to invest for the medium term
, want to do some trade, then you should take
special care of this level of 5350.
Come on sir, the next counter
here is of ICICI LBR General Insurance
Company.  Here too, the results of Quarter 2 were
announced.  There was a
jump of about 18% in profit.  The
company had a profit of Rs 820 crore in this quarter 2.
Apart from this,
we saw a slight decline in the gross direct premium income.  There
is a slight decline of about 1.9% and the
income through gross direct premium was
around ₹6596
crore.  Apart from this, there was a
jump of about 12% in his total income.  It
was ₹6582 crore and the
combined ratio was somewhere around
105%
105.1% which was 104.5% last year
and the company has also announced an interim dividend of
₹6.5 per share.  In such a situation,
Sir, how do you see ICICI LBD
for fresh entry right now?
Overall looks like a good stock.
And if we talk about the sector,
I feel that a good revival has been seen in the insurance sector.
After GST reforms, a very good momentum has been
seen.  One if we talk about index
is custom base index.  There is a
good consolidation range visible today as the session
breaks.  And
the way the numbers have come, if we talk about ICICI LBAT, it has been
quite impressive.  The stock
price is also showing a very good impressive move.  The
breakout of the important level of 1950 is visible in today's session.
We are currently trading around 2000
and we have also crossed the 2000 levels
in today's session.  So I feel
that the way momentum was seen in the stock price,
the way
volume was built in today's session and if we
talk about custom index, a very good
breakout is also being seen.  So this
is a good stock reversal confirmation is
visible in ICICI LBD.  So, if there is
any decline from a good level,
around 1950-60, 50
to 60 points below, then you can add a position there also.
I feel that you should maintain a
stop loss of 1890 and
in the coming time we may see levels of 2200 and 2220.   So, the
stop loss of 1890 and the target of 1220 can be
seen in ICICI LBD.
Even today, a rise of about 7.5% is being
seen here.  So
if you want to enter for short term, then
here the entry
levels, stop loss and
target have been told to you.
You can enter yourself in this on behalf of Yagnish Sir.
But yes, before making any investment,
you should do your own research and also
take advice from your financial advisor.  Only after that you should enter any type
of trade.  Let's move ahead sir
and there is a company here called Thyro Care
Technologies.  Sir, there was a jump
of about 81% in the profit of Thyrocare Technologies.
And the
profit last year was Rs 26 crore.  This year it has increased to Rs
47.8 crore.  Revenue also
saw a growth of around 22% and the
company also announced an interim dividend of
₹7 per share.
Despite this, if we look at Thai Technologies today, there
is a slight rise here.  We are seeing a rise of 1% here
and the current market price is
₹1276.  What
should be done here, sir?
Ah, according to which a very good
gap up opening was seen in the stock.  But
selling is being seen from higher levels
and the stock was facing resistance at a very important
level 1450, which was previously an
important swing high, and
after opening at the same level, a decline is being
seen from there.  So this is a negative
price action is not a bullish sign.  According to me,
I feel that we should wait a little.  The
stock price might possibly
move into a slight consolidation zone.
After that we will make a new fresh approach in it.
So for now it would be advisable to avoid it.
So, you have to avoid it for now.
Sir, the next counter, now many
results here are also going to be announced
today.  Let's talk about them too.  The
first name here is
IRFC, which is Indian Railway Finance
Corporation.  The results here are going to be
announced today.  Therefore,
somewhere or the other, this stock remains
in focus today.  And along with this,
IRCTC also
comes into focus somewhere.  And if we talk about Indian Railway Finance
Corporation, today
we are seeing a rise of about 1.5% in
IFC, sir.
How are you looking at IFC PSU company Navratna company sir
and dividend announcement is also being discussed
here sir.  What should be done
with these levels sir?   According to
which
railway stocks have been underperforming.  For quite some
time now, we have been able to see that if we
look at the custom index, it
was in a consolidation zone and if we look at the stocks specific, then
many stocks have formed a bottom in the
month of August and somewhere or the other, it is
showing a good reversal from there.
Even in IRCTC, a similar scenario is being seen.
Important bottom formation was
seen in the month of August.  Higher bottom
formation series is also being seen.
Sir, somewhere or the other,
reversal is being seen within the index custom index.
Within the railway stocks,
a good bottom formation is also being seen in the stock of Sem Verfc.
However,
I feel that its confirmation is the resistance of 1130 130 cent
swing high.  Previously
this has been a high form.  So I think there will be a
breakout of 130.  So
we can say that its trend reversal is confirmed for the mid term.
So this is a good stock.  I
feel that there is a small range of
127.50. If there is a breakout after the result announcement in the short term,
then
we may see a good upside move.
1130 will be the first resistance and 1135 will be the
second resistance which
we can take as per the target.  So my overview
is positive.  Bullish on this stock.  We will
wait a little for the breakout of 12750.   So,
IFC results are going to be announced today.
You have also been told the targets.
Levels have also been mentioned.  If you
want to enter, then the level of 127 is going to be very important for you.
From there, you can see the targets of 130 and 135
coming inside IRFC.
Let's move ahead sir and whatever other
announcements are coming today.
Axis Bank remains in focus here.
And apart from this, let us first talk about HDFC Life Insurance Company
Axis Bank.
Sir, what is the view being formed regarding Axis Bank
?  We have consistently seen that there has been some underperformance
within Axis Bank.
What should be done in this sir?
Ankit ji's overall view on private sector banks
is positive.  The way Nifty
Bank is performing, a
good move is being seen in the index.  One of the
stocks that I feel is Axis Bank can
give a good performance in the coming time.
So my overall view is positive and as per the
chart structure formed, there was
an important level of around 1150-1160,
we have broken out of that and we are sustaining the same level now.
So according to me the
view is positive.  However, if we talk about today's two
trading sessions, today's and the
previous day, then negative
price action is being seen somewhere or the other.  But
we are still holding the important levels.
So according to me the view should be bullish.
We will keep it inside it.
In the coming time, I feel that the levels of 1200 and 1220,
which previously formed resistance, can be
seen in Axis Bank.
So the overall view
is positive.  We have to maintain stop loss at 1140.  So,
you have to keep a stop loss of 1140 here
and the targets that you have, up to 1200, you
can see them coming here in Axis Bank
and continuously Yash Sir, I feel that the downside is also less here
because if we
look at our one year return, then the return is only about 1.15%
in 1 year, so the downside
is limited and if we talk about the upside, then Sir,
if we want to go above 1200 in the mid term, then
what will be the targets for the mid term,
Sir, here, yes
exactly Ankit Ji, as per what you
told that the risk is less.  There is a favourable risk
reward ratio here and
if we breakout above 1200, then I feel that on the
upside we can see levels up to 1300 and 1320 which have previously
formed swing highs.